<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Badabings</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/blockquotes/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 01 Nov 2014 01:54:12 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.7</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Post With a Blockquote</title>
		<link>/blockquote/</link>
					<comments>/blockquote/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[John Doe]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 01 Nov 2014 01:54:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Category #1]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockquotes]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://demo.studiopress.com/genesis/?p=7</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[This is an example of a WordPress post, you could edit this to put information about yourself so readers know where you are coming from. You can create as many posts as you like in order to share with your readers what is on your mind. This is an example of a WordPress post, you [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>This is an example of a WordPress post, you could edit this to put information about yourself so readers know where you are coming from. You can create as many posts as you like in order to share with your readers what is on your mind.</p>
<blockquote><p>This is an example of a WordPress post, you could edit this to put information about yourself so readers know where you are coming from. You can create as many posts as you like in order to share with your readers what is on your mind.</p></blockquote>
<p>This is an example of a WordPress post, you could edit this to put information about yourself so readers know where you are coming from. You can create as many posts as you like in order to share with your readers what is on your mind.</p>
<p>This is an example of a WordPress post, you could edit this to put information about yourself so readers know where you are coming from. You can create as many posts as you like in order to share with your readers what is on your mind. This is an example of a WordPress post, you could edit this to put information about yourself so readers know where you are coming from. You can create as many posts as you like in order to share with your readers what is on your mind.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/blockquote/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Sample Post With a Blockquote</title>
		<link>/blockquote-2/</link>
					<comments>/blockquote-2/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[John Doe]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2013 01:54:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Category #1]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Blockquotes]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://demo.studiopress.com/genesis/?p=7</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[This is an example of a WordPress post, you could edit this to put information about yourself or your site so readers know where you are coming from. You can create as many posts as you like in order to share with your readers what is on your mind. This is an example of a [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>This is an example of a WordPress post, you could edit this to put information about yourself or your site so readers know where you are coming from. You can create as many posts as you like in order to share with your readers what is on your mind.</p>
<blockquote><p>This is an example of a WordPress post, you could edit this to put information about yourself or your site so readers know where you are coming from. You can create as many posts as you like in order to share with your readers what is on your mind.</p></blockquote>
<p>This is an example of a WordPress post, you could edit this to put information about yourself or your site so readers know where you are coming from. You can create as many posts as you like in order to share with your readers what is on your mind.</p>
<p>This is an example of a WordPress post, you could edit this to put information about yourself or your site so readers know where you are coming from. You can create as many posts as you like in order to share with your readers what is on your mind. This is an example of a WordPress post, you could edit this to put information about yourself or your site so readers know where you are coming from. You can create as many posts as you like in order to share with your readers what is on your mind.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/blockquote-2/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
